Preliminary Guide to the Frank C. Brown Papers, 1899 - 1943 UA.29.02.0043
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Frank C. Brown papers
1899-1943
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Brown, Frank Clyde, 1870-1943
UA.29.02.0043
30 Linear Feet
Frank Clyde Brown (1870-1943) served as Professor of English at Trinity College and Duke University, and as Comptroller and University Marshall of Duke University. He oversaw the initial construction of Duke University's West Campus and the renovation of East Campus. Brown also founded the North Carolina Folklore Society. The Frank C. Brown Papers contain correspondence, logs, diaries, reports, lantern slides, notebooks, clippings, a scrapbook, and other materials. While some papers relate to teaching and English department activities, the bulk of the collection concerns the construction of Duke University, including correspondence with the Horace Trumbauer architectural firm, builder and manufacturer information, construction progress reports, travel diaries of visits to other campuses, and records of James B. Duke's views on architecture and involvement in campus planning. English.
Access Restrictions
Scrapbook and lantern slides are fragile. Handle with care. Contact University Archives staff for assistance.
Provenance
The Frank C. Brown Papers were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1948-1974.
Biographical Note
Frank Clyde Brown (1870-1943) served as professor, departmental chairman, university administrator, and collector of folklore. He was born October 16, 1870, in Harrisonburg, Va. to John Michael and Emma Catherine Liskie Brown. He earned an A.B. from the University of Nashville in 1893, and M.A. and Ph.D. degrees from the University of Chicago in 1902 and 1908. In 1909, he began his career as professor of English at Trinity College (Durham, N.C.).
Brown organized the North Carolina Folklore Society in 1913, and served as its secretary-treasurer, program chairman, and primary collector until his death in 1943. The Frank C. Brown Collection of North Carolina Folklore, published by Duke University Press in seven volumes between 1952 and 1964, represents Brown's lifetime of collecting.
Between 1924 and 1930, Brown was deeply absorbed in the expansion of Trinity College into Duke University, serving as a member of the Building Committee of the Board of Trustees and as the first comptroller of the University. As comptroller, he acted as the liaison for architects, contractors, suppliers, administrators, and faculty in the designing, construction, and equipping of the redesigned East Campus, which became the Woman's College, and of the completely new West Campus. Brown is credited with contributing many original ideas to the building plans, foremost of which was the discovery of the nearby Hillsborough, N.C. stone and the recommendation that this material be utilized in the construction of the Gothic West Campus. He also served as university marshal, planning all major formal celebrations and entertaining numerous distinguished visitors to the new university.
Brown's published works include Elkanah Settle: His Life and Work (1910) and Ballad Literature in North Carolina (1915). In 1893 he married Ola Marguerite Hollis, who died in 1928, and in 1932 he married Mary Henkel Wadsworth. Brown died on June 3, 1943.
[Portions of this text are taken from a biographical sketch of Frank Clyde Brown written by William E. King.]
Collection Overview
The Frank C. Brown Papers include both Personal papers and Subject files relating to his career as a student, professor, and folklorist and also to his role in the construction of the Duke University campuses. The Personal papers series includes correspondence, biographical information, writings, addresses, lectures, clippings, diaries, coursework, blueprints, and slides. It includes correspondence with the Horace Trumbauer architectural firm, manufacturers' literature, construction progress reports, diaries of trips made in 1924 and 1926 to look at other campuses, and a lantern slide presentation on the campus. This series contains records documenting James B. Duke's views on architecture and his involvement in the planning of the campus. Also present is a diary/scrapbook kept by Brown and President William Preston Few during a 1924 tour during which they visited some twenty colleges and universities around the Eastern United States.
The Subject files series contains the alphabetical office files of Frank C. Brown. The bulk of the files pertain to the construction of the Duke University campuses and include information on planning, design, building materials, furnishings, builders, manufacturers, and vendors. A few items interfiled in the Subject files series relate to Brown's activities as a faculty member and as a member of professional and academic organizations.
Related Material
Frank Clyde Brown Papers.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Operations and Maintenance Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Horace Trumbauer Architectural Drawings.
University Archives, Duke University.
College buildings -- Planning; Blueprints; Lantern slides; Diaries; Scrapbooks; Campus planning -- North Carolina -- Durham; Clippings (information artifacts); Duke University. Comptroller; Duke University. University Marshal; Duke, James Buchanan, 1856-1925; Trumbauer, Horace, 1869-1938; Brown, Frank Clyde, 1870-1943; Duke University -- Buildings; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- History
- Personal papers, 1899-1943
  Scope and Contents note
  The Personal papers series includes correspondence, biographical information, writings, addresses, lectures, clippings, diaries, coursework, blueprints, and slides. Some material relates to Brown's work as a student, professor, and folklorist, but the majority of the papers concern Brown's role in the construction of the Duke University campus. It includes correspondence with the Horace Trumbauer architectural firm, manufacturers' literature, construction progress reports, diaries of trips made in 1924 and 1926 to look at other campuses, and a lantern slide presentation on the campus. This series contains records documenting James B. Duke's views on architecture and his involvement in the planning of the campus. Also present is a diary/scrapbook kept by Brown and President William Preston Few during a 1924 tour during which they visited some twenty colleges and universities around the Eastern United States. In addition, the collection features speeches and writings by others about Brown and on the North Carolina Folklore Society.
  - Biographical sketch (Box 1)
  - I Knew Frank Clyde Brown (Box 1)
  - Fifty Years of the North Carolina Folklore Society (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1909-Mar. 1928 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 1928-June 1943 and undated (Box 2)
  - Shakespeare Tercentenary Celebration, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Proofs of grammar book (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes and memorabilia (Box 2)
  - Trumbauer correspondence [reference copies], Dec. 1924-Aug. 16, 1926 (Box 3)
  - J. B. Duke views on design (Box 3)
  - Trumbauer correspondence [reference copies], Aug. 16, 1926-Sept. 27, 1926 (Box 4)
  - Diaries on construction of campus, [2 vols.] (Box 4)
  - Travel log (Box 4)
    Idea book from Brown's trip to the University of Chicago containing his observations on buildings and furnishings.
  - West Campus construction (Box 5)
    - Progress reports, March-Sept. 1927 (Box 5)
    - Hardware (Box 5)
    - Paint, stone, etc. (Box 5)
    - Blueprints (Box 5)
  - M.A. Thesis: The Literary Influence of Byron on Shelley, 1902 (Box 6)
  - Data on Elkanah Settle; Drawings and plates from The Empress of Morocco (Box 6)
  - Addresses and lectures (Box 6)
  - Clippings (Box 6)
  - Course notebooks [Univ. of Chicago], 1899-1901, 1906-1907 (Box 7-8)
  - Trumbauer correspondence [originals], 1924-1927 (Box 9)
  - Construction (Box 10)
    - Manufacturers' literature (Box 10)
    - Log books, 1925-1926 (Box 11)
  - Glass slides: Woman's College and Duke Forest (Box 12)
  - Glass slides: Duke University and Duke Forest (Box 13)
  - Diary of W. P. Few and F. C. Brown trip to various universities to collect data for construction of Duke University, March-April 1924 (Box 14)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    FRAGILE: Handle with care.
  - Views and plans of various colleges and universities (Box 15)
- Subject files, ca. 1924-ca. 1930
  This series contains Subject files of Frank C. Brown. The bulk of the files pertain to the construction of the Duke University campuses and include information on planning, design, building materials, furnishings, builders, manufacturers, and vendors. A few items interfiled in the Subject files series relate to Brown's activities as a faculty member and as a member of professional and academic organizations.
  Arrangement note
  Ordered alphabetically.
  - Untitled folders, 5 folders (Box 16)
  - Acoustic Correcting (Box 16)
  - Adding Machines (Box 16)
  - Addresses of Secretaries, Comptrollers, and Other University Officials by Institutions (Box 16)
  - Air Compressors (Box 16)
  - Air Filters (Box 16)
  - Air Washers (Box 16)
  - Allocations of Offices and Classrooms (Box 16)
  - Alms Basin (Duke University) (Box 16)
  - Alpha Chemical Company (Box 16)
  - Alteneder and Sons, Theo. [Drawing Instruments] (Box 16)
  - Alumni Activities (Box 16)
  - Alumni: Duke University (Box 16)
  - American Association of Teachers of Journalism (Box 16)
  - American Association of University Professors (Box 16)
  - American Blower Company (Box 16)
  - American Council on Education (Box 16)
  - American Engineering Company (Box 16)
  - American Hospital Association (Box 16)
  - American Literary Journal (Box 16)
  - American Seating Company (Box 16)
  - Amplifiers and Loud Speakers (Box 16)
  - Anchors - Floor (Box 16)
  - Animal Cages (Box 16)
  - Anson Brick and Tile Company (Box 16)
  - Antiques (Box 16)
  - Applications
    - Architects (Box 16)
    - Athletics (Box 16)
    - Biology (Box 16)
    - Boarding Houses (Box 16)
    - Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Draughtsman (Box 16)
    - Education (Box 16)
    - Engineering (Box 16)
    - Fraternities (For Housing in New Dormitories) (Box 16)
    - Gardener (Box 16)
    - General (Box 16)
    - Hostesses in Dormitories (Box 16)
    - Laundrymen (Box 16)
    - Maids (Box 16)
    - Mathematics (Box 16)
    - Medical School and Hospital (Box 16)
    - Music (Box 16)
    - Publicity (Box 16)
    - Purchasing Agents (Box 16)
    - Space in New Classrooms (Box 16)
  - Appointments: Preachers (Box 16)
  - Arboretum and Museum of Natural History (Box 16)
  - Architects (Box 16)
  - Architects: List Of (Box 16)
  - Architectural Forum (Box 16)
  - Architectural Record (Box 16)
  - Architecture (Box 16)
  - Art Supplies (Box 16)
  - Association of College and University Unions (Box 16)
  - Association of University and College Business Officers of the Eastern States (Box 16)
  - Athletic Goods (Box 16)
  - Athletics For Women (Box 16)
  - Atlantic Screen and Weather Strip Company (Box 16)
  - Auctioneers (Box 16)
  - Austin-Heaton Company [burlap bags] (Box 16)
  - Autoclaves (Box 16)
  - Automobiles: Estimates on Cost (Box 16)
  - Automobile Accessories (Box 16)
  - Avera Bible Lectures (Box 16)
  - Awnings and Tents (Box 16)
  - Badges For Workmen (Box 16)
  - Bain-Kimball-Milam Company [memorials, marble and granite] (Box 16)
  - Bakelite (Box 16)
  - Baker and Taylor Company Company [books] (Box 16)
  - Baldwin, R.L., Company [draperies] (Box 16)
  - Balers (Box 16)
  - Ball-Bearing Trolley (Box 16)
  - Baltimore Electric Blue-Print Company (Box 16)
  - Barbershop and Barber Supplies (Box 16)
  - Barney, E.E. [suction pump] (Box 16)
  - Barth, L., and Company [hotel equipment] (Box 16)
  - Bassett, L.P. [door screens] (Box 16)
  - Bathroom Cabinets: Miami (Box 16)
  - Bausch and Lomb Optical (Box 16)
  - Bayer Company, The [valve stems] (Box 16)
  - Beaty, Guy M. [Pipe and Boiler Coverings] (Box 16)
  - Beck Engraving Company (Box 16)
  - Bed Braces, Chair Braces, and Guides (Box 16)
  - Bells (Box 16)
  - Bibles (Box 16)
  - Bids and Estimates
    - Cement Floor-- Science Building (Box 16)
    - Painting (Box 16)
    - Pipe Covering (Box 16)
    - Printing (Box 16)
    - Southgate Hall Floors (Box 16)
  - Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company (Box 16)
  - Bills of Lading (Box 16)
  - Bills Payable (Box 16)
  - Bills Payable: Clements (Box 16)
  - Bills Receivable (Box 16)
  - Binoculars (Box 16)
  - Bird Supplies (Box 16)
  - Bittner, W.A., Company [electrical sales agents] (Box 16)
  - Blackboards (Box 16)
  - Blacksmith Equipment (Box 16)
  - Blank Forms: University Receiving and Purchasing Departments (Box 16)
  - Blinds (Box 16)
  - Block, N., and Company [Iron, Steel, Metal, and Second-Hand Machinery] (Box 17)
  - Board of Education: Durham County (Box 17)
  - Board of Health (Box 17)
  - Boiler Coating (Box 17)
  - Bonsal, W.R., Company [gravel and sand] (Box 17)
  - Book Shop (Box 17)
  - Bookcases (Box 17)
  - Books: Architecture (Box 17)
  - Books: Business (Box 17)
  - Books: Business-- Baker and Taylor (Box 17)
  - Books: Furniture (Box 17)
  - Borden Brick and Tile Company (Box 17)
  - Botany and Zoology, Chemistry, and Physics: Specifications (Box 17)
  - Bradford and Company, Incorporated [felt, leather, textile, and paper specialties] (Box 17)
  - Bradshaw, William [payment] (Box 17)
  - Branscombe, Professor B.H. [freight and drayage] (Box 17)
  - Branson (Box 17)
  - Breedlove, J.P. [librarian] (Box 17)
  - Breneman Company [shades] (Box 17)
  - Brent, C.S., Seed Company (Box 17)
  - Brooms (Box 17)
  - Brown, Frank C. (Personal) (Box 17)
  - Brumby Chair Company (Box 17)
  - Brushes (Box 17)
  - Budd-Piper Roofing Company (Box 17)
  - Building Correspondence: Yale (Box 17)
  - Building Correspondence: Harvard (Box 17)
  - Building Correspondence: Cornell (Box 17)
  - Building Materials
    - Brick (Box 17)
    - Cement (Box 17)
    - Freight (Box 17)
    - Lime (Box 17)
    - Lumber, Millwork (Box 17)
    - Lumber, Millwork-- Bids and Estimates (Box 17)
    - Marble (Old Campus) (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
    - Plastering (Box 17)
    - Roofing (Box 17)
    - Sand (Box 17)
    - Stone (Box 17)
    - Stone Option (Box 17)
    - Stucco (Box 17)
    - Tile (Box 17)
    - Woodwork (Box 17)
  - Building Plans: Auditorium (Old Campus) (Box 17)
  - Building Plans: Bids and Estimates (Buildings) (Box 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds (Box 17)
  - Buildings: Construction Engineers (Box 17)
  - Buildings, Cheap (Box 17)
  - Buildings: Cost Of (Durham City Schools) (Box 17)
  - Buildings: Old and New Campuses (Names Of) (Box 17)
  - Buildings, Old Campus: Acceptances and Authorizations (Box 17)
  - Caldwell, Edward F., and Company [gas and electrical light fixtures] (Box 17)
  - Cambridge Botanical Supply Company (Box 17)
  - Caraleigh Phosphate and Fertilizer Works (Box 17)
  - Carolina Hardware Company (Box 17)
  - Carolina Heating and Engineering Company (Box 17)
  - Carolina Motor Club (Box 17)
  - Carolina Power and Light Company (Box 17)
  - Carolina Radiator and Body Glass Works (Box 17)
  - Carolina Standard Gas Products Company (Box 17)
  - Cary Lumber Company (Box 17)
  - Central Contracting Company (Box 17)
  - Charak Furniture Company (Box 17)
  - Chicago Pump Company (Box 17)
  - Christian and Harward [furniture] (Box 17)
  - Christian and King Printing Company (Box 17)
  - Christian, L.M. [payment] (Box 17)
  - Christian Transfer Company (Box 17)
  - Christmas Sign Shop (Box 17)
  - City of Durham (Box 17)
  - Clancy, J.R., Incorporated [stage screws] (Box 17)
  - Clark, S.T. [payment] (Box 17)
  - Clifford Smith Company, The [manufacturers and jobbers] (Box 17)
  - Coleman's [Drug Store] (Box 17)
  - College Entrance Examination Board [CEEB] (Box 17)
  - Colson Company of Baltimore [trucks] (Box 17)
  - Commencement (Box 17)
  - Continental Furniture Company (Box 17)
  - Cotrell and Leonard [cap and gown] (Box 17)
  - Cotton Goods Supply Company (Box 17)
  - Cox and Sons and Viving [caps and gowns] (Box 17)
  - Crane Company [Globe valves] (Box 17)
  - Cranford, Dr. W.I. [wood] (Box 17)
  - Credle, S.M. [payment] (Box 17)
  - Crouse-Hinds Company [flood light parts] (Box 17)
  - Crumpacker, A. [payment] (Box 17)
  - Daily Analysis Reports
    - Week Ending 10/28/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 11/04/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 11/11/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 11/18/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 11/26/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 12/02/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 12/09/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 12/16/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 12/23/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 12/30/26 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 1/06/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 1/13/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 1/19/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 1/28/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 2/03/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 2/10/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 2/17/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 2/24/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 3/03/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 3/10/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 3/17/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 3/24/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 4/07/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 4/14/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 4/21/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 4/28/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 5/05/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 5/12/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 5/19/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 6/02/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 6/09/27 (Box 17)
    - Week Ending 6/16/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 6/23/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 6/30/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 7/07/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 7/14/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 7/21/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 7/28/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 8/04/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 8/11/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 8/18/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 8/25/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 8/31/27 (Box 18)
    - Week Ending 9/07/27 (Box 18)
  - Davis [drafting] (Box 18)
  - Day Log: Heating Plant, August, 1927 (Box 18)
  - Day Log: Heating Plant, September, 1927 (Box 18)
  - Dermott Heating Company (Box 18)
  - Devereux Studios (valences and curtains) (Box 18)
  - Dewey Brothers, Incorporated [founders and machinists] (Box 18)
  - Dietzgen, Eugene, Company [tracing cloth, wire] (Box 18)
  - Dillon, James L. and Company [photographic prints] (Box 18)
  - Dillon Supply Company [mill supplies and machinery] (Box 18)
  - Display Stage Lighting Company (Box 18)
  - Dize Awning and Tent Company (Box 18)
  - Dodge Coach Receipts (Box 18)
  - Doehler Furniture Company (Box 18)
  - Dowdee, J.W. [galvanized iron tank, roofing and sheet metal works] (Box 18)
  - Doyle Florist (Box 18)
  - Duke, Mrs. B.N. (Box 18)
  - Duke Construction Company (Box 18)
  - Duke Endowment, The (Box 18)
  - Duke University (Box 18)
  - Duke University Heating Plant (Box 18)
  - Duke University Store (Box 18)
  - Dulany-Vernay Company [japanese lanterns] (Box 18)
  - DuPont, DeNemours, and Company, E.I. [paints and varnishes] (Box 18)
  - Durham, History of (Box 18)
  - Durham Auction Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Battery and Electrical Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Blue Printers (Box 18)
  - Durham Book and Stationary (Box 18)
  - Durham Brazing and Welding Works (Box 18)
  - Durham Foundry and Machine Works (Box 18)
  - Durham Granite Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Hosiery Mills (Box 18)
  - Durham Ice Cream Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Iron Works (Box 18)
  - Durham Lumber Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Mattress Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Morning Herald (Box 18)
  - Durham Paint Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Public Service Company (Box 18)
  - Durham Seed House (Box 18)
  - Durham Shade Works (Box 18)
  - Durham Sign Works (Box 18)
  - Durham and Southern Railway (Box 18)
  - Durham Sun (Box 18)
  - Electric Blueprint Company (Box 18)
  - Ellerbrock, Lawrence, Incorporated [hotel and institution kitchen serving equipment] (Box 18)
  - Elliott, Charles H. and Company [office supplies] (Box 18)
  - Elliott Furniture Company (Box 18)
  - Ellis- Stone and Company [cloths and spreads] (Box 18)
  - Erwin Cotton Mills Company (Box 18)
  - Erwin, W.A. [mules, wagon, and harness] (Box 18)
  - Express (Box 18)
  - Faulkner, Littlejohn [signs] (Box 18)
  - Federal Equipment Company (Box 18)
  - Firch Dustdown Company [cleaning supplies] (Box 18)
  - Five Points Automobile Company (Box 18)
  - Five Points Drug Company (Box 18)
  - Floor Covering (Box 18)
  - Floor Covering: Linoleum (Box 18)
  - Floor Grips (Box 18)
  - Floor Machinery (Box 18)
  - Floors and Flooring (Box 18)
  - Floors: Finished (Box 18)
  - Flour (Box 18)
  - Flowers, Artificial (Box 18)
  - Fogle Furniture Company (Box 18)
  - Folk--Lore (Box 18)
  - Follow-Up: Loans (Box 18)
  - Ford U Drive It System (Box 18)
  - Foremen's Daily Reports
    - 9-19 October, 1926 (Box 18)
    - 20 October-22 November, 1926 (Box 18)
    - 23 November-31 December, 1926 (Box 18)
    - 1 January-11 February, 1927 (Box 18)
    - 12 February-21 March, 1927 (Box 18)
    - 22 March-30 April, 1927 (Box 19)
    - 1 May-27 June, 1927 (Box 19)
    - 28 June-16 August, 1927 (Box 19)
    - 17 August-10 September, 1927 (Box 19)
  - Forestry and Forest Development (Box 19)
  - Forsyth Furniture Lines, Incorporated (Box 19)
  - Foundations and Scholarships (Box 19)
  - Frames: Picture, Pier, Mantle, et cetera (Box 19)
  - Fraternities: Finances (Box 19)
  - Fraternity Houses (Box 19)
  - Frederick Post Company [drawing materials, blueprint paper] (Box 19)
  - Freight Bills (Box 19)
  - Freight Shipments (Box 19)
  - Fuller, Ralph [payment for surveying] (Box 19)
  - Fuller Brush Company (Box 19)
  - Furniture
    - Auditorium (Box 19)
    - Auditorium- New Campus (Box 19)
    - Benches (Box 19)
    - Chairs (Box 19)
    - Classroom (Box 19)
    - Decorations (Box 19)
    - Dining Room (Box 19)
    - Dormitories (Box 19)
    - Folding Chairs and Tables (Box 19)
    - General-Desks (Box 19)
    - General-Prices (Box 19)
    - Library (Box 19)
    - Office (Box 19)
    - Pianos (Box 19)
    - Polish (Box 19)
    - School (Box 19)
    - Steel (Box 19)
    - Stools (Box 19)
  - Furniture and Other Materials Available (Box 20)
  - Game Preserve (Box 20)
  - Gardens (Box 20)
  - Gas: Cost in Other Cities (Box 20)
  - Gas and Electricity: Charges and Rates (Box 20)
  - Gas and Oil: Prices and Contracts (Box 20)
  - Gas Meters: Calorimeters (Box 20)
  - Gateway's Stores, Incorporated (Box 20)
  - General Education Board (Box 20)
  - General Electric Company (Box 20)
  - General Equipment Company (Box 20)
  - Glass (Box 20)
  - Glassware (Box 20)
  - Glynn-Johnson Corporation [door holding equipment] (Box 20)
  - Gonella Marble and Granite Works (Box 20)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company (Box 20)
  - Grand Central Garage (Box 20)
  - Grant, Charlers B. [plumbing and heating] (Box 20)
  - Grant, John [bookseller] (Box 20)
  - Gray, G.W. [horse-shoer] (Box 20)
  - Gray and Creech Incorporated [mill agents- distributors] (Box 20)
  - Graybar Electric Company (Box 20)
  - Green, Robert M., and Sons [soda fountains] (Box 20)
  - Greenhouses (Box 20)
  - Greensboro Hardware Company (Box 20)
  - Griggs Sales Company, Incorporated (Box 20)
  - Grime, Edwin M. [payment of expenses] (Box 20)
  - Grounds (Box 20)
  - Guides (Box 20)
  - Gymnasium: Old Campus-- Maintenance (Box 20)
  - Hall, B.M.--Correspondence (Box 20)
  - Hall, B.M.-- Requisitions and Time Sheets (Box 20)
  - Hardware
    - Butts (Box 20)
    - Doors (Box 20)
    - Fences (Box 21)
    - Locks (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Paints and Glass-- Prices and Estimates (Box 21)
    - Paint Finishes (Box 21)
    - Paints, Varnishes, and Glass (Box 21)
    - Paints-- Vortex Manufacturing Company (Box 21)
    - Paints for Automobiles (Box 21)
    - Panic Bolts (Box 21)
    - Prices (Box 21)
    - Sash Pulleys (Box 21)
    - Screens (Box 21)
    - Screens (Box 21)
    - Shades (Box 21)
    - Shades (Box 21)